- Hey. - Yeah. Yeah, okay. Sure.
-嘿 -嗯、嗯、好啦，當然
Look, can we talk about what happened here last night?
聽著，我們可以談談 昨晚這裡發生的事嗎？
Sure. Just give me a second to get all huffy and weird like you.
當然，給我幾秒鐘讓我變得跟你一樣 怒氣衝天、怪裡怪氣的
You believe that whoever did something last night did what they did or didn't do?
你敢相信某某人昨天晚上 做了某某事嗎？
Okay, you really don't know what I'm talking about?
你真的不知道我在說什麼嗎？
- No. - Okay. Last night, after the party..
-不知道 -好的，昨天晚上，在派對過後…
I saw Rachel kissing that jerk from her office out on your balcony.
我看到瑞秋在你家的陽台上 親她辦公室的那個混蛋
Our balcony? Seriously?
在我家陽台？真的嗎？
That's so funny. I told Monica we should put lights on our balcony..
真是好玩，我告訴摩妮卡我們應該 在陽台上加個燈的
and she said, "No, no. It's too cold. Nobody will go out there." And I said:
可是她說「不不，外面太冷了 沒有人會站到外面去的」，然後我說…
"Maybe if we put some lights out there they will."
「如果我們加個燈 或許就會有人了」
Right, that's what I came over to talk about. I saw Rachel kissing some guy..
對，那就是我要談的事 我看到瑞秋親吻一個男的…
on your balcony, even though there were no lights!
就在你家陽台上 即使那裡一片漆黑！
So are you gonna talk to her?
那你要跟她談談嗎？
Why? Why should I? I mean, if she wants to move on, that's fine.
為什麼？為什麼我要？ 如果她要找尋新生活，沒關係
You know when "that's fine" sounds true? When someone yells it and spits.
你知道「沒關係」要怎樣說才有 說服力嗎？噴著口水用力吼
No, I'm serious. I mean, if she wants to date people, fine. I don't care.
不，我是說真的，如果她想要跟 別人約會，沒關係，我不在乎
But at least she could have told me.
但是至少她要跟我說啊
You know, I've been putting my life on hold and concentrating on Emma.
你知道的，我的生活都已經停擺 注意力完全集中在艾□身上
But if she wants to go out there kissing guys she barely knows, then so will I.
但是如果她要去親那些不是 很熟的男人，我也要那樣做
Very funny! Ross is gay!
很好笑！羅斯是同志！
No, no. Good, so you're moving on.
不，很好，所以你也要有新的生活了
Do you have any idea where you're moving on to?
你知道你要怎麼樣過新生活嗎？
I've got plenty of opportunities.
我是有很多機會的
Just now, there was some woman at the coffeehouse smiled at me.
剛剛在咖啡廳就有個女人對我笑
And then the other day on the subway, a woman "accidentally" sat on my hand.
還有一天在地鐵，有個女人 「不小心」坐到我的手
Dude, don't rub my face in your crazy single life.
老兄，別再跟我說你瘋狂的單身生活了
And there's an anthropologist at school..
還有，在學校有個人類學家
who totally came on to me during the interdepartmental potluck dinner.
在跨部門餐會的時候 不停在勾搭我
Why did I get married?
我為什麼要結婚呢？
The One Where Monica Sings
rainystar壓制iPod-MP4
Hey, let me ask you guys something.
嘿，讓我問你們一個問題
I'm having new headshots taken tomorrow.
我明天要拍新的大頭照
The photographer said she thinks I should have my eyebrows waxed.
攝影師說，她覺得我應該要修眉毛
Is that weird for a guy?
男生那樣做是不是很怪呢？
- Well, it depends. - On?
-嗯，那要看情況 -什麼情況？
On how far along he is in the sex-change process.
看他是在變性過程中的什麼階段囉
No, I totally disagree. I think it's fine for a guy to do something like that.
不，我完全不同意 我覺得男生那樣做沒有什麼
Especially an actor.
尤其是演員
I mean, not that you need to. Your eyebrows are..
我不是說你有那個必要，你的眉毛…
Stop it, you guys. Stop staring, you're freaking me out.
你們別這樣，別盯著我看 要嚇死我了
Your knuckles are kind of hairy too.
你的手指上也有毛
Oh, man, now I have to get those done too?
天啊，現在我也要除這些毛嗎？
- Wow, talk about high maintenance. - You dye your hair.
-哇，你要做的改造可不少啊 -你也染髮啊
- I'm a woman. - Double standards!
-我是女人啊 -雙重標準！
Before I forget, are you coming to Mike's piano bar tonight?
差點忘記 你今晚會去麥克的鋼琴酒吧嗎？
- Only if I don't have to get up and sing. - But everybody sings. It's so fun.
-只要我不需要上台唱歌 -但是大家都要唱歌啊，會很好玩的
Last time, this adorable old man got up there, forgot all the words, flipped out..
上次有個可愛的老先生上台 忘了所有的台詞 糗呆了
and everyone booed him off the stage. It was so funny.
然後大家就噓他下台，真是好玩
Look, I'm not good at singing.
聽著，我唱歌不行的
Oh, what's the matter? You scared? You afraid I'm a better singer?
喔，怎樣？你怕了嗎？ 怕我唱的比你好嗎？
You afraid I'm gonna beat you at singing?
怕我會用唱歌打敗你嗎？
Nope. Nope. It's not working on me.
不，這招對我沒用
Wow, I must be growing up.
哇，我一定是長大了
Okay, fine. Just please come and support Mike. You don't have to sing.
好吧，就過來支持麥克就好了 你不需要唱歌
So I don't have to sing, and I can just sit there and pass judgment on others?
所以我不用唱歌，而且還可以坐在那裡 討論、批評其他人？
- While drinking. - I'm there.
-還可以一邊喝酒 -我要去
Hi, you guys. Listen, I really need your help.
嘿，你們好 我需要你們的幫忙
I think I did something really stupid.
我想我做了一件很蠢的事
Well, yes, Rachel, but you got something so beautiful out of it.
嗯，是的，瑞秋，但是至少它很漂亮
No, not that. I kissed Gavin last night.
不，不是那件事 我昨晚親了蓋文
- My God. - You kissed him?
-我的天 -你親了他？
Yeah, it was after the party, we were on the balcony..
是啊，就在派對結束之後 我們在陽台上…
Wait, wait, wait. I was at home the whole time. How did I miss that?
等等，我一直都在家，為什麼沒看到？
Well, it was the end of the party. You were probably ironing wrapping paper.
派對才剛結束 你可能正忙著燙平包裝紙
Oh, yeah.
喔，是啊
So how did you end up kissing?
那你們怎麼會親起來的呢？
We were all alone and he was being really nice..
我們單獨在一起，然後他又很體貼
- and he gave me this scarf. - I thought you hated him.
-然後又送我這條圍巾 -我以為你討厭他
Well, there is a thin line between love and hate..
愛與恨之間只有一線之隔
and it turns out that line is a scarf.
而結果，那條線就是這圍巾
Are you thinking of starting something up with this guy?
你在想要跟這男的交往嗎？
I don't know. It's so complicated. I work with this guy.
我不知道，真是太複雜了 這男的是我同事耶
I have the baby, and I have Ross. I don't know what to do.
我已經有小孩，有羅斯 我不知道該怎麼辦
And I have to be at the office and see Gavin in 10 minutes.
而我再十分鐘就要進辦公室見到蓋文了
Sounds like you need to think about what you want and talk to Gavin.
聽起來你應該想想 要怎麼跟蓋文說了
- And you definitely should talk to Ross. - Or..
-而且你一定得要跟羅斯說 -或者…
I could call in sick and not deal with it at all.
我可以打電話請病假，那就不用管了
Wow! Five months maternity leave, you're back for four days..
哇！請了五個月的產假 才回去上班四天…
kiss a co-worker and call in sick. They are lucky to have you.
親了一個同事就請病假 他們有你這個員工真幸運
- Hi. - Hi.
-嗨 -嗨
- I'm here for my eyebrow appointment. - Name?
-我有預約修眉毛 -什麼姓名？
Chandler Bing.
錢德賓
Okay, very good.
好的，很好
Have a seat right here, Mr. Bing, and Sonya will be right with you.
請先坐一下，賓先生 桑妮亞很快就出來了
Okay. Thanks.
好的，謝謝
I touched the stuff.
我碰了那東西
I'll take care of it.
讓我來處理
Thanks.
謝謝
So do you..? Do you get a lot of guys in here?
那你們… 你們這裡有很多男生會來嗎？
- Oh, absolutely. - Oh, good.
-喔，當然 -喔，很好
- You looking to meet somebody? - All right, let's just do this.
-你想要認識他們嗎？ -好了，我們開始吧
Okay, we'll get to the wax in a minute.
好的，我們等一下再上熱蠟
First, I want to tweeze some of the strays, okay?
首先我要先拔一些雜毛，好嗎？
- Now, this may sting just a little bit. - I have an extremely high threshold..
-這可能會有點痛 -我很可以忍痛…
Holy Mother of God! Oh, my face! My face!
媽媽咪啊！ 喔，我的臉！我的臉！
I'm all right. I'm all right. I'm all right.
我沒事，我沒事，我沒事
It's just a bit of shock, that's all.
只是有點嚇到，沒什麼
- But I'll be fine. You can go again. - Okay.
-但是我沒事，你可以繼續了 -好的
Sorry.
抱歉
Damn it, woman!
可惡，你這女人！
It's the most eligible man in New York. How's the moving on going?
全紐約最有身價的單身漢來了 新生活進行得如何呢？
Not well. I went on the subway again and someone did sit on my hand..
不太好，在地鐵上 又有個人坐到我的手
but that person was neither female nor wearing pants.
但是，這個人既不是女性 也沒有穿內褲
Maybe you're going about this the wrong way. I mean, think about it:
或許你完全錯估情勢了 我是說，你想想看
Single white male, divorced three times, two illegitimate children.
單身白種男性，離婚三次 有兩個非婚生子女
The personal ad writes itself.
你應該要自己心裡有數的
You know, that's funny. Yeah. So do you think you'll ever work again?
真是好笑，是啊 那你覺得你這輩子會找到工作嗎？
What are you doing? You know I can only dish it out.
你在幹嘛？ 你知道我們會鬥個沒完的
I can't believe Rachel just moved on and didn't say anything to me.
我不敢相信，瑞秋就這樣拋下 我們的過去，而且沒有跟我說
Maybe she didn't move on.
或許她並沒有拋下
Maybe that kiss was just an impulsive, one-time birthday thing.
或許那只是衝動之下吻的 過生日才發生一次的那種
No, a month ago, she gave her number to some guy in a bar.
不，一個月以前，她還把電話號碼 留給一個在酒吧認識的男的
- Did she go out with him? - No. When he called..
-她有跟他出去嗎？ -沒有，當他打電話來時…
I threw the message away.
我把留言丟了
The high road.
真是厲害啊
All right, you know what? Enough. Enough talking. I have to get moving.
你知道嗎？夠了 說夠了，我要展開新生活了
Hey, check out those two blonds over there. Hey, come with me.
嘿，瞧瞧那兩個金髮美眉 嘿，跟我一起過去
Are you trying to get everybody divorced?
你要害每個人都離婚嗎？
You don't have to do anything. It'll just be easier if it's two of us.
你不用做什麼 但是我們兩個一起過去會比較好
Like college, remember? First, you break the ice with some kind of a joke..
就像大學一樣，記得嗎？ 你先過去說笑話熱場面
so they know you're the funny one. I swoop in with interesting conversation..
讓她們知道你是好玩的人 然後我再插入有趣的話題
so they'll see that I'm the brilliant, brooding, sexy one.
讓她們才知道我既聰明 有教養又性感
I thought I got to make the jokes.
我還以為說笑話是我的專利
- Don't you have to be at work? - Oh, come on.
-你不用上班嗎？ -拜託，走吧
Hello. Hi, my name's Chandler. This is my friend Ross right here.
哈囉，我叫錢德 這是我朋友羅斯
We were wondering..
我們在想…
if you're up for it, we only need six more people for a human pyramid.
如果你們有興趣的話 我們還需要六個人來完成人體金字塔
Swoop. Swoop.
接手，接手
Hey, I notice you're reading the paper.
嘿，我注意到你在看報紙
Another flood in Europe, huh?
歐洲又有水災了，對嗎？
Here's a question:
問題來了
Would you rather drown or be burned alive?
你寧願被淹死還是被活活燒死？
- I'm sorry, we're just leaving. - Okay.
-很抱歉，我們要走了 -好的
We still got it.
我們還是寶刀未老
- Who is it? - Gavin. I brought you some soup.
-是誰？ -蓋文，我帶一些湯來給你
- Why? - I heard you were sick.
-為什麼？ -我聽說你生病了
Oh, right! Hold on, let me just clean up in here a little bit.
喔，對！等一下 讓我先整理一下
Hello, Gavin.
哈囉，蓋文
I missed you at work. How you feeling?
今天上班我好想你，你還好嗎？
I'm not gonna lie to you, I'm pretty sick.
我不想對你說謊，我病得很重
Oh, good. Because I was having a totally paranoid moment..
喔，好，因為我還擔心…
where I thought you called in sick to avoid me.
你是在裝病逃避我
Oh, no, no, no.
喔，不、不、不
So I had fun last night.
我昨晚很愉快
So did I.
我也是
Exactly how contagious is this thing you have?
你的病到底傳染性有多高呢？
Is it a cold from standing on the balcony, or did a monkey bite you?
是因為站在陽台上受涼了 還是被猴子咬呢？？
- It's just a cold. - Do you have a fever?
-只是單純的感冒 -有發燒嗎？
Let me see.
讓我看看
What? What is it? What's the matter?
怎麼？怎麼了？怎麼回事？
What's Ross doing to you in that picture?
在那張照片中 羅斯在對你做什麼？
Oh, he's dusting me with a fossil brush.
喔，他在用化石刷子幫我除塵
He thought it would be funny.
他覺得那樣很好玩
- Right. Right. - Yeah.
-是啊 -是的
- Ross. - Yeah.
-羅斯 -是啊
What's the deal with you guys? I don't wanna get in the middle of anything.
你們之間有什麼嗎？ 我不想要當第三者
You're not getting in the middle of anything. Don't worry about Ross.
你不是第三者，別擔心羅斯
Hide! That's Ross! Hide!
快躲！是羅斯！躲起來！
- Hide! Hide! - Yeah, but you said not to worry..
-躲起來！躲起來！ -但是你說不用擔心…
I lied and I'm not sick either! Just stay behind the curtain!
我說謊，而且我也沒有生病！ 躲到窗簾後面！
- Hi. - Oh, Molly. You're not Ross.
-嗨 -喔，莫莉，不是羅斯
No. I'm here to take Emma to your mother's, remember?
不是，我是來接艾□到你媽家的 記得嗎？
Right. Yes, yes.
對，是的，是的
- Don't panic. - What?
-別緊張 -怎麼了？
There is a man behind your curtain.
有個男人躲在窗簾後面
- I have Mace in my purse. - No, that's okay! No, no, no.
-我皮包裡有防狼噴霧 -不，沒關係！不、不、不
This is my business associate Gavin being silly. Come out from behind there.
那是我同事蓋文在發神經 出來吧！
Hi. Gavin. Pleased to meet you.
嗨，我叫蓋文，很高興認識你
It was my idea to stand there.
是我要站在那裡的
- Hello. I'll just go get Emma. - Okay.
-哈囉，我去帶艾□ -好的
So..
那麼…
- why did I have to hide? - I thought it was Ross.
-為什麼我要躲呢？ -我以為那是羅斯
I thought there was nothing going on between you.
我以為你們之間已經沒有什麼了
There isn't. There totally isn't.
是沒有，完全沒有
You hear keys in the hall and you jump like a bronco coming out of the chute.
你聽到鑰匙轉動的聲音 就像野牛一樣跳了起來
I used to be a rodeo clown.
我做過鬥牛士
All right, look, Gavin..
好的，聽著，蓋文
I guess I felt guilty that you were here..
我想，你在這裡 讓我覺得有罪惡感
which I shouldn't.
我這樣想是不對的
You know, Ross and l are not in a relationship..
你知道的，羅斯跟我並沒有在交往
but he is the father of my child. And, you know..
他是我孩子的父親，而且…
we do live together. And plus, there's just so much history, you know?
我們還住在一起，還有 我們有太多過去了，你知道嗎？
It's just.. I don't know.
只是…我不知道
- I'm sorry. I'm just all over the place. - It's okay.
-我很抱歉，我頭腦很不清楚了 -沒關係
It's probably not my place, but can I give you a piece of advice?
這或許不關我的事 但是我可以給你一個建議嗎？
- Yes. - You should talk to Ross about all this.
-好的 -你應該跟羅斯談這件事
People keep saying that.
大家都這樣說
I'm sorry, Gavin.
我很抱歉，蓋文
Don't be.
別抱歉
It's just bad timing.
只是現在不是好時機
So seriously, rodeo clown?
講真的嗎？鬥牛士？
One of the best, ma'am. One of the best.
技術最棒的，小姐 技術最棒的
（鋼琴酒吧與夜總會）
Oh, she's my girlfriend. That's not just how we do it here.
喔，她是我女朋友 不只是在台上而已
I'm gonna take a little break, and when we come back..
我要休息一下，當我們回來時
we've got Kenneth singing "I Touch Myself."
肯尼將要演唱「我自摸」
I'm not here to judge.
我不是來當評審的
- You have got to sing. - No, I told you I can't.
-你一定要上台唱 -不，我告訴過你我不行
But you would have so much fun. And you have a really nice voice.
但是你會很喜歡的 而且你的聲音很好啊
- When have you heard me sing? - All the time, when you're cooking.
-你是何時聽到我唱歌的？ -常常，當你在煮飯的時候
- What? - Yeah, you're always singing:
-什麼？ -是啊，你總是一邊唱著…
Yummy, yummy, yummy I've got love in my tummy
好吃，好吃，好吃 我肚肚裡有愛愛
Yeah, I do rock that one.
是啊，我那倒是唱得不錯
Isn't there just a little part of you that wants to get up there?
你難道一點都不想要上去唱嗎？
Just a little. But, God, it's so scary.
一點而已，但是老天，好可怕喔
I don't even know what I would sing.
我根本不知道要唱什麼
- Well, I've got a book around.. - "Delta Dawn."
-嗯，我有一本歌本在… -「破曉時分」
（中央咖啡廳）
Hi. I couldn't help but notice, but that's an unusual necklace.
嗨，我不得不注意到 你特別的項鏈
You already hit on me an hour ago.
你一個小時前就來搭訕過了
Right. So that's a firm no?
沒錯，所以確定不要嗎？
I don't believe this. I just keep striking out.
我不敢相信，我一直被判出局
I don't get it either.
我也不敢相信
I mean, you're obviously desperate.
我是說，很明顯地你是很飢渴了
You're asking women how they wanna be killed.
你問女人她們想要如何死法
This is great. Rachel's gonna keep kissing guys..
太棒了，瑞秋繼續去親男人…
until she finds the one she wants, and I'm gonna die alone.
直到她找到她想要的男人 而我將孤單地死去
By drowning or..?
是淹死還是…
- Why would he break up with me? - I don't know, sweetie.
-他為什麼要跟我分手呢？ -我不知道，親愛的
All I ever wanted was to just love him and have him love me back.
我要的只不過是愛他，希望他也愛我
I mean, am I so unlovable?
我是說，我有這麼不值得愛嗎？
- Wow. - I know.
-哇 -對了
All right. That was Kenneth with his..
好了，以上是肯尼所帶來的…
much too literal rendition of "I Touch Myself."
即興表演「我自摸」
Coming up next, we've got Monica singing "Delta Dawn."
接下來是摩妮卡演唱「破曉時分」
Wait. I can't sing in front of all these people.
等等，我不能在這些人面前唱
Just pretend they're not even here. It's okay.
假裝他們不在，沒關係的
Once that spotlight hits you, it's so bright, you won't see anyone anyway.
一旦聚光燈照到你，會很亮的 反正你也看不到任何人
Hi, I'm Monica. And I'm going to be singing "Delta Dawn."
嗨，我是摩妮卡 我要唱的是「破曉時分」
- Can you totally see through her shirt? - Like an x-ray.
-你可以看穿她的上衣嗎？ -像X光一樣
Bad day not to wear a bra.
今天不是不穿內衣的好日子
I'm calling about the advertising job.
我打來詢問廣告工作的
Yes, I realize it would be entry level.
是的，我瞭解這是基層職務
Oh, so would I actually have to wear the chicken suit?
喔，所以我真的要穿小雞裝嗎？
I need your help.
我需要你的幫忙
Wow, it seems serious.
哇，看起來很嚴重
What seems to be the problem, Ashley Judd?
是怎麼了呢？艾希莉賈德？
I'm getting new headshots taken. So I went to get my eyebrows shaped.
我要照新的大頭照 所以我去修了眉毛
I'm sorry. Moment to make fun of that, please.
很抱歉，讓我笑一下吧
I may be a sissy, but I'll still pound you into the ground.
我看起來可能娘娘腔的 但是我還是可以海扁你的
Look, it hurt so bad, I could only let her do one eyebrow, and now..
聽著，好痛喔，我只能讓她做一邊 所以就…
they don't match!
兩邊不對稱了！
It's like a baby caterpillar chasing its mama.
就像是毛毛蟲寶寶在追媽媽一樣
You got to help me out, okay? Look, I have a magic marker.
你得要幫我，好嗎？ 看，我有麥克筆
Fill in the skinny one so I don't look stupid for my pictures.
幫我把細的這邊劃粗 照起相來才不會很蠢
Okay, first of all, this is green.
好的，但是，首先這是綠色的
- What the hell am I supposed to do?! - I will help you out..
-我他媽的該怎麼辦呢？ -我會幫你的
but you have to promise you won't tell anyone what I'm about to tell you.
但是你要答應我 不會把我要告訴你的事說出去
What? What?
什麼事？什麼事？
Okay.
好了
You know how most kids get their allowance from mowing the lawn..
你知道大部分的小孩都是利用除草 或是倒垃圾什麼的…
or taking out the garbage? Well, I earned mine..
來賺取零用錢 而我賺零用錢的方式…
by plucking the eyebrows of my father and his "business partners."
就是幫我父親 還有他的「合夥人」拔眉毛
Oh, my God.
喔，我的天
Yeah, well, I guess you don't need my help, Victor-Victoria.
好的，我猜你不需要我的幫忙了 喬伊美眉
No, no, no. I do. I do. I need your help.
不、不、不，我要，我要 我需要你的幫忙
But, Chandler, I don't know if I can take any more plucking. It hurt so bad.
但是錢德，我不知道能不能 再忍受拔毛，真的好痛
Not with my combination of ice cubes, aloe vera and my gentle..
安啦，有我的冰塊跟蘆薈配方 加上…
self-loathing touch.
連自己也厭惡的溫柔接觸
I'm sorry, the song's over.
我很抱歉，歌唱完了
- Did you see me up there? - Every little bit of you.
-你有看到我在上面嗎？ -全身上下看透透
I can't believe I sang in front of people and they liked me.
我不敢相信我在大家面前唱歌 而且他們喜歡我
Did you hear that guy shouting, "Look at those tips"?
你們有聽到還有人大喊 「瞧瞧那些小費（意同乳頭）」嗎？
I mean, did I really help you get a lot of tips?
我是說，我有幫你多賺小費嗎？
Sure.
當然有
- Mon, not that you didn't sound good.. - Good?
-摩妮卡，不是說你唱的不好… -不好？
Didn't you hear them? I was great!
你沒有聽到他們的叫聲嗎？ 我棒透了！
Thank you so much for making me do this. That is the best gift ever.
謝謝你逼我這樣做 這是我有過最好的禮物了
Also a good gift: underwear.
內衣也會是好禮物
Thank you so much for letting me do this.
謝謝你讓我過來
Public bathrooms freak me out. I can't even pee, let alone do anything else.
公共廁所讓我覺得很惡 我根本沒有辦法上廁所，更別說其他的
But what's great is you don't mind talking about it.
但是更棒的是，你根本不介意說出來
It is so amazing that I met you on the same day that Eric broke up with me..
這真是太神奇了，在我跟艾瑞克分手的這一天，我就遇見了你
because it's like, you lose a boyfriend, and you get a boyfriend.
這就是，失去一個男朋友 又得到一個男朋友
No, don't worry. This is not some rebound thing. I am totally over Eric.
你不用擔心，這不是補貨療傷法 我已經完全不愛艾瑞克了
Good choice, Ross.
挑的真好，羅斯
Hey. Hi. There you are.
嘿，嗨，你在家
- I've been looking for you everywhere. - Hello. Well, here I am.
-我到處在找你 -哈囉，我在家
My mom is not bringing the baby back until 9:00.
我媽到九點才會把孩子帶過來
So I was hoping you and I could have a chance to kind of..
所以我希望，我們可以有機會來…
- Somebody here? - Oh, yeah. That's Michelle.
-有人在這裡嗎？ -是的，是蜜雪兒
- Who? - Oh, just this woman I've been seeing.
-誰？ -喔，是我最近在約會的女生
- You've been seeing someone? - Yeah, didn't I mention that?
-你有在約會？ -是啊，我沒有提過嗎？
I mean, we haven't been going out too long..
我是說，我們並沒有約會很久
but there's this amazing connection between us.
但是我們之間有很奇妙的感情
I mean, in fact just before you came in, she called me her boyfriend.
而且就在你進來之前 她才說我是她男朋友
I thought it was a little too soon, but also, it felt kind of nice.
我是覺得有點太快，但是覺得也不錯
What are you taking amoxicillin for?
你為什麼要用青黴素呢？
How great is this? You're already comfortable enough..
真是太棒了，你已經可以自在的…
to look through my stuff.
偷看我的東西了
I'm sorry, Michelle, this is my roommate, Rachel.
很抱歉，蜜雪兒 這位是我室友，瑞秋
And I'm also Emma's mother.
而且我也是艾□的母親
- Who's Emma? - I told you about my daughter.
-艾□是誰呢？ -我跟你說過，是我的女兒
This is your daughter?
這位是你女兒？
I could be your new mommy.
我可以當你的新媽媽喔
And done.
好了
Oh, my God.
我的天
I didn't feel a thing. Hey, are you still looking for a job?
我根本都沒感覺 嘿，你還在找工作嗎？
Because you could tweeze circles around that sadistic bitch at the salon.
你比那個沙龍的臭娘們會拔多了
- Thanks. Wanna see what it looks like? - Yeah.
-謝謝，想要看看嗎？ -好啊
They totally match. They look great.
對稱了，很好看耶
They look great. How you doing?
看起來真棒，你怎麼做的？
Yeah, I think it looks pretty good. I was a little worried I was..
是啊，我覺得看起來挺不錯的 我本來有點擔心會…
uncovering a birthmark right about there..
讓這上面的胎記露出來
but it turned out to be a little piece of chocolate.
但原來那只是一點巧克力渣
- Chandler, thank you so much. - No problem.
-錢德，真是感謝你 -不用客氣
Listen, that was a pretty girlie hour we just spent.
聽著，我們剛花了一小時做娘們的事
We should do something manly to make up for it.
我們應該做一些男人的事來彌補
Yeah.
是啊
- Curl my eyelashes. - Yeah!
-把睫毛夾卷 -好啊！
For my next song, I think I'll sing something a little more upbeat, all right?
下一首歌我想唱比較輕快的，好嗎？
How about the Pointer Sisters' "I'm So Excited"?
唱Pointer姐妹的「脫掉」怎樣呢？
And make it bouncy.
彈得活潑一點哦
Well, you can probably take care of that on your end.
嗯，你自己就可以辦得到了
I'm sorry I'm late. You'll understand when you see Joey.
很抱歉我遲到了，等一下你看到喬伊 就知道為什麼了
Honey, you're just in time. I'm about to sing another song.
親愛的，你正好趕上 我正要唱另一首歌
- Really? In front of all these people? - And they love me.
-真的？在所有人面前嗎？ -而且他們很喜歡我
- Oh, my God. - She gives the people what they want.
-我的天 -她給的正是他們想要的
All right, watch.
好的，看著
Are those my wife's nipples?
那是我老婆的乳頭嗎？
Isn't that funny? I didn't see that before. I wouldn't have let her go up again.
真是好玩，我之前怎麼沒有注意到？ 要不然我不會讓她上去的
I've gotta stop this.
我必須要制止她
Who cares? They still love me.
管他的，他們還是愛我
You, touching yourself! Out!
你，在自摸！出去！
Wow! She does that a lot.
哇！她這麼常上廁所
Ross, you didn't tell me you were a doctor.
羅斯，你沒有告訴我你是博士
Wait a minute. You haven't even told her you are a doctor yet?
等一下，你還沒有告訴她 你是博士？
How long have you known her, like an hour?
你認識她多久呢？一個小時嗎？
Actually, about an hour and a half.
事實上是一個小時半
I told you it wasn't long, but there's an amazing connection between us.
我告訴過你不久，但是我們之間有 很奇妙的感覺
You feel that too?
你也有感覺到嗎？
- I thought that that was just me. - Are you kidding?
-我以為只是我單方面而已 -你開玩笑嗎？
- Do you wanna go away this weekend? - We'll see.
-你想要這週末一起去度假嗎？ -再說
Ross, what's going on here?
羅斯，這是怎麼回事呢？
Are we just bringing strange women back to the apartment now?
我們現在是可以帶陌生女人回家了嗎？
I don't know. Are we just kissing guys on balconies?
我不知道，我們現在是可以 在陽台上親吻男人了嗎？
- How do you know about that? - Through the magic of sight.
-你怎麼會知道呢？ -我有千里眼
- I was here, putting our child to sleep.. - Emma.
-我在這裡，把我們的女兒哄睡 -艾□
When I looked through the window and saw you kissing a guy..
當我從窗戶看過去 就看到你在親一個男的
you've known for what, a week?
一個你認識有多久的男生，一星期嗎？
God, is that what this is all about? You bring her up here to get back at me?
天啊，這就是原因嗎？ 你帶她回來報復我嗎？
No, actually, see, I had to pee because I can't use public bathrooms..
不，事實上是我要上廁所 而我又不能上公共廁所
- because of the doody parasites. - Okay, Michelle, it's time to go.
-因為有寄生蟲 -好了，蜜雪兒，你該走了
- Well, call me. - Okay.
-那，打電話給我 -好的
Wait, you don't have my phone number.
等等，你沒有我的電話
You know what? If it's meant to be, I'll guess it.
你知道嗎？如果是命中注定 我會猜到的
Bye-bye.
再見
Score.
高招
Did you not like her? Because I was hoping we could come..
你不喜歡她嗎？ 我還希望我們可以…
to your kissing parties on the balcony.
去參加你的陽台親吻派對
I can't believe you are making a big deal about this. It was one kiss!
我不敢相信你竟然小題大作 只不過是一個吻！
- One guy. One time! - Oh, really?
-跟一個人，一次而已！ -喔，真的嗎？
- Yeah. - Oh, really?
-是啊 -喔，真的？
Oh, yeah.
喔，真的
- What about the guy from the bar? - Who?
-那個酒吧認識的男的呢？ -誰？
The guy you gave your number to.
你給他電話號碼的那一個
- How do you know about that? - Because he called here looking for you.
-你是怎麼知道的？ -因為他打來找你
So don't tell me kissing this guy from work is a one-time thing.
所以別跟我說，你親這個男同事 只是一次而已
Because you've been out there in bars and on balconies..
因為你又在酒吧，又在陽台上…
for over a month now. And you don't even have the courtesy to tell me.
已經一個多月了 而你根本就沒有禮貌性地告訴我
- Why didn't I get that message? - What?
-為什麼我沒有拿到留言？ -什麼？
From the guy in the bar? Why didn't I get that message?
那個酒吧的男的留言？ 為什麼我沒有拿到留言？
Because I folded it up and put it in my pants pocket.
因為我折起來放到褲子口袋裡了
Do you not look there?
你沒有去找過嗎？
Ross.
羅斯
I never gave it to you.
我沒有拿給你
Why?
為什麼？
- I don't know. - Oh, God, you know what? I don't..
-我不知道 -天啊，你知道嗎？我不…
Who do you think you are? Who are you to decide..
你以為你是誰呢？誰讓你有權決定…
what messages I should or should not get?!
什麼留言我該收或是不該？
Who am I? I'm the guy who's taking care of our baby..
我是誰？我是那個照顧我們孩子的人
- while you're at bars meeting guys! - I cannot believe you.
-而你卻在酒吧跟男人混！ -我真不敢相信
I actually came in here hoping to have a mature conversation with you about us.
我回來希望能夠 跟你成熟的談談我們之間
But I can't do that with someone who hides my messages..
但是我不能跟會藏我留言 還會帶瘋女人…
and brings crazy women back to my apartment!
回我公寓的人談！
Hey, none of the sane ones wanted to come back with me!
嘿，正常的人沒有一個要跟我回來！
That's not the point, okay? The point is..
這不是重點好嗎？重點是…
you are the one who moved on and didn't tell anyone.
是你拋下我們的過去，而你卻沒有說
Oh, God, Ross, this is just so messed up.
天啊，羅斯，這真是糟透了
What is wrong with us? When people hear about our situation, they ask:
我們是怎麼了？ 當大家知道我們的情況都會問…
"You live together, but you're not a couple, yet you have a baby?
你們住在一起，不是一對 但是你們又有小孩？…
Isn't that weird?" And I say, "No. It's not, because it works for us."
不是很奇怪嗎？「我會說 」不會，我們都沒問題
But you know what? This doesn't work.
但是你知道嗎？是有問題的
- In fact, this is the opposite of working. - Clearly.
-事實上，還正好相反咧 -的確如此
And you know..
你也知道
we said that we would live together as long as this makes sense..
我們有說過只要一切沒問題 我們就會一直住在一起
and maybe this just doesn't make sense anymore.
然而，或許一切不再是沒問題了
Yeah, maybe not.
是啊，或許不再是了
So, what do you wanna do?
那你想要怎樣呢？
Hi.
嗨
Can Emma and I live here for a while?
我跟艾□可以過來住一陣子嗎？
God.
天啊
- Of course. - Thank you.
-當然可以 -謝謝你
Your eyebrows look weird.
你的眉毛很奇怪
So you'll just touch yourself for anything, then?
所以不管怎樣，你都會自摸啦